<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Pages on winnipegR</title>
    <link>/page/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Pages on winnipegR</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/page/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Research</title>
      <link>/research/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/research/</guid>
      <description>publications  &amp;ldquo;When Obstinacy is a Better (Cognitive) Policy,&amp;quot; Philosophers&amp;rsquo; Imprint, 2017. Associated Mathematica notebook &amp;ldquo;Confirmation,&amp;rdquo; with Franz Huber, in Oxford Bibliographies Online, 2017. DOI: 10.1093/OBO/9780195396577-0024 &amp;ldquo;Understanding Probability: A Review of Darrell Rowbottom&#39;s &amp;lsquo;Probability&amp;rsquo;,&amp;rdquo; Metascience, 25(2):331-333, 2016. DOI: 10.1007/s11016-016-0073-x. &amp;ldquo;A Normatively Adequate Credal Reductivism,&amp;rdquo; Synthese, 191(10):2301-2313, 2014. DOI: 10.1007/s11229-014-0402-9. Historicist Theories of Scientific Rationality with Carl Matheson, in Edward Zalta (ed.), The Stanford Encyclopedia of Philosophy, Fall 2014 edition.  selected presentation activity (2018) &amp;ldquo;Becoming an Insight-driven Organization&amp;rdquo; (with primary guest speaker Mark Dufresne).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>I am currently a data scientist for the City of Winnipeg, working with each area of the City to promote data driven decision-making; reducing costs and improving the services the City delivers.
Before that, I worked in the private sector as the Retail Business Intelligence, Analytics and Machine Learning Lead for the Dufresne Group, where I was responsible for (i) building an analytics department, (ii) shaping data governance strategy, (iii) advising CEO and management team by generating key insights contributing to organizational growth, and (iv) implementing advanced data projects for the organization.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Search</title>
      <link>/search/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/search/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>